You call me from the static, between the waking and the fall, I found you in the
I was already waiting In the margins of your pain
Psychies nightmares come alive With the beautiful things go to survive
You've been the darkness, I'm in the light
Everybody gotta take names in the air like a trial. I didn't make buying them out pick a side prove
You're one of us funny how fast that support turns to pressure and disgust. I said, I don't know the story
I'm not signing up on claims you want instant verdicts. I don't play those games
No paper then I'm asking for more that defense. That's me checking the floor
And when I don't bend to the grass to create start rewriting what I'm supposed to be
You were back in me, building me like in the show
Till I didn't follow where you wanted me to go
This is my platform, not your community
You don't get to vote on what I believe
You want control, dressed up as a unity
I see the strings, I don't agree
You draw your lines and expect me to trace it
Call it standards, I call it stage
Now it's noise trying to speak over me
But this is mine, not yours
long way, if sane voices yell in different names on the stage, everyone knows yeah, everyone
says but nobody stops to question the threat. Proof in the DMs I didn't review, or proof
you decided was already true. You want me to act on a crowd made case then punish me
when I don't keep pace. Then a few people now I'm afraid. Maybe I'm done with the games
Like in the show, till I didn't follow where you wanted me to go
This is my platform, not your community
You don't get to vote on what I believe
You won't control dressed up as a unity
I see the strings, I don't agree
You draw your lines and expect me to trace it
Calling standards, I call it stage
Now it's noise trying to speak over me
But this is mine, not your community
You say I'm wrong for what I allow, but who made you judge, jury, and now executioner live in my chat, nah
to keep you agreeing with me
You drew your lines and I didn't chase it
You called it loss, I replaced it
Now it's me standing where I choose to be
Yeah, this is why I'm not your community
Hi, Jamie. Unfortunately, the membership is on hold right now, but it should be back
shortly, maybe a few months. Discord doesn't work? Yeah, I'll update that.
I'll go through my Discord list. Yeah, but if you could...
Do the exclamation point cash app, but I'm also I'll make one for song requests. I'm doing for readings, too
How is everyone doing hi Jamie, how are you good to see you? I'll fix the nightbot today after after the show I
Did like unhide some people
For another chance, but you know
I can't I'm not going to continue with the harping or the attacking and it's like I'm also like people that I see in other chats like just totally bad mouth in me.
How are we doing. Let me see 1213 people. I don't know it's like it seems like it's been.
Yeah, it's just interesting. I mean it's like I don't know
For someone with as good a hair of mine like I you know, I'm my hair
I'm not I don't have a gray hair and 45 years. I don't have like one gray hair. I do have my beard and stuff, but I
Don't dye my hair or anything. It's all
Natural it's like
What is with like this, you know Kate Kate is doing these pictures of me as like, you know, Syraxie
I mean really it's like I guess it's like yeah the most like, you know
Insult trying most kind of insulting thing you can try to say but it's like so like off the low-cow thing. It's like
Sire, it's just like I'm so not that you know, it's like I can play a clown sometimes, but I know I'm doing it, right?
but um
That's sire. I'm not I'm not a retarded goblin. I mean that's a little bit of a stretch. I mean
I guess psyche and TSY is that I guess
Cyrexcology, I don't know
Watching basketball. Well, here's Rudy. I don't know. I heard today. Oh, he's using his cats as props
His cats are staring at the wall. There's there. They're not there. They're starving that all they do is eat
You know rats. He doesn't love them. They're just there's props and stuff like that
Anyone if anyone actually watches like they know, I mean, it's like yeah, they'll say this kind of stuff just a troll
it's like
Is they think it's gonna hurt the most and bring up bring up tricks and stuff like that which is like, you know, of course
But it's like just me knowing that it's just like trying to hurt me. It's like really doesn't it doesn't hurt me
I know the truth. Yeah, there's Rudy and Lola's over here
there
The North's right here
We're all sitting around not using them as props there. They're all happy a free will to be where they want to be
And you'd like to be here, you know
And unfortunately, you know
having outdoor cats too, there's dangers and there's potential for, has anybody
had an animal ever run away? It's like it's not like neglect, right? I mean it's
like not at all. It's like basically giving us some freedom. And there's, you
know, it's just like imagine a parent like the, and I know it's a cat, you know,
cats and children are different things, but
I can make an analogy imagine like you know if people just kept their kids locked up and oh because the world is dangerous
and bad things can happen, you know
fortunately they can but
At the same time, you know, is it healthy to leave and locked in the house all day and like a little house with their
They can't like put their feet in nature and they can't roll around in the sun and they can't you know chase a squirrel climate tree
You know
go do their business outside all kinds of stuff. I mean it's like I decided that
it'd be better for them to have the option to go inside and outside and these cats like to spend
most of the time inside but you know they like to go outside too a little bit. Tricks was going
out a little bit more and more. Hey Loki, could I have got a leash and took them for a walk?
Yeah but that's you know cats don't really like to be leashed.
It's like, you know, there are harnesses and stuff you can buy for cats, and thanks for your opinion. It's fine. I
Yeah, I would love to just be able to walk the cats and stuff like that
But it's not that easy to walk cats. I mean or else you'd see cats being walked around. It's not really easy
It's like it's kind of difficult sometimes. I've tried it. I've tried it and it's not the easiest thing
They're not dogs
They're they don't like to be lead, you know
Yeah, I can have the cats in backpack, but it's like that's the same thing
I'm gonna have the cat locked in the bubble backpack. I mean, it's it's like
You should see like when I open the door and they're cute and stuff like that
But when I open the door and they go out and they just like you just like lay it roll around in the sun
They like to go do their business outside. They like to you know, sometimes
You know, this other cat comes out and they all like to go
Visit visit some other cat that's there. I don't know, but they're all fixed all these cats are fixed and so these cats are all
Good to see you go key. I hope that we can
You know how about a good good starting over kind of thing
You know, I know motion up motions get high and the people have a lot of thoughts and stuff and
But at the end of the day, it's like I just got I don't like to be told what to do
I have to like, you know do it on my come to my own decision to do things and so I can't be bullied into doing it
And you know a lot of these bullies were just are just like people that have harassed me a lot
So they're just waiting for something to pounce on and so I have to kind of learn how to sort sort
Between that and you know, there's even buddy trolls, you know, it's like it's not an easy community
But I guess none of them really are you know
But yeah, I did unban all your accounts.
I went in and out that I know of, you know,
you might have more, but I didn't know.
But yeah, I unban some people, like RG,
I unbaned RG, I unbaned.
So a few people that I think maybe I,
maybe I caught up in the crossfire a little bit
or something like that.
And so,
Yeah, it's hard when you know, and the people want to give their opinion, but it's like give to understand. It's like it's very
When people are piling on and and pressuring me to make decisions and stuff like that
I just need to slow down a little bit. I am I talking to Brandon on the panel
um
And you know, and it's like maybe he hasn't maybe he did do some very questionable
things
But at the same time I'd like to talk to him about that and get his side of the story
It's like not really fair to have like people silenced and then it's like there's just one side of the narrative being pushed
Because then anything can be added to that and it can get exaggerated and we know how in this community
We know we know everybody can level accusations and
You know, I just want to be fair. I want to let everyone have a chance to talk and stuff
I didn't try to silence opposition, but I was saying, you know
Hey, we're moving on from this topic and I made my decision and people kept harping harping harping this stage
Oh, and then when you're calling the names and they can say terrible things
I was I didn't block anybody that was polite politely said anything, you know
and
So I mean
Hi. Hi. Hi. You said meow. Hi. I'm going to be up to you. Hi. Does your meow? You look quite meow.
Come sit. Oh, baby.
Sorry.
Yeah.
My cats, my cats are like, my cats like the camera type. They like being on camera.
They can, they, I think they didn't see themselves in the TV. And so
I kind of like it
Yeah, I'm ready. I'm gonna sit down. I sit down. Oh, give me that one or sit down
That's it out. Yeah, yeah
Sam I was like, oh his cats are staring at the walls. Hello. Oh my gosh
Thank you. I like good times. I don't know if that's the real good times for
What did Doofu?
How are you?
Thank you for being in the chat today already. Yes, I had some good shorts I published today. I published a lot of good shorts today.
They're pretty funny. Well, they're pretty funny.
Yeah, I think we had the untrackable transformation. Let me see if I can find that one.
Yeah, I did some I did some AIs yesterday of some people like an untrackable to turn up pretty funny
I want to see that here
Okay, let's see it, this is hilarious.
There we go.
Okay, got it.
That's a little, fuck, that thing now actually,
this should be when I met him.
Show him information.
Yeah.
No, no, that's the middle.
That was a year ago.
That's now.
and go back to his photo when I first met him.
We can see the whole transformation, my man,
the whole process.
I don't know if you've ever seen a photo of him.
I think what YouTube did to one track of him
when they met him, he was a young handsome fellow.
Well, how about taking a photo?
All of them were so hot.
They were so hot.
Look at you now, my man.
Not so hot, are you?
No.
I know it from here.
There you go, there you go, there you go, a year into YouTube and boom, three years later.
There you go.
That was untratable.
That's him now.
Do you want to see Lola get under the covers with me?
Here's where she does.
Okay, Lola.
You want to go under the covers?
Come on.
I'll go under the covers.
Watch.
Lola.
Oh
She did it. She's gonna see Lola get under the covers.
You know what's really happening is that it's not a random drama. This is a control battle.
So my my side of the story is I decided what happened on my platform. The critics are going
to say you're part of a shared ecosystem with standards. Well, you know, YouTube is the ecosystem.
Not any of this like, what is it? I'm supposed to like collaborate with Beatis Kitties and Samman
same community right and so it's like actually well they're ethating by the way I don't know if
you're aware of that they are ethating
Yeah, okay. So the core accusation letting Brandon and Q rock out of my chat is like, you know, what's really happened?
Watching Mario Lopez make it in the shower on anything that is what's up? How are you doing?
We're having a fun night. Yeah, watching and watching Mario Lopez in the shower
That is has to be like one of now. He's a kind of cheesy. He's on extra and stuff like that
He's like where they're really either Ryan Seacrest. I got Samoan Ryan Seacrest
But back in the day when it was like more like, you know, he was like same brother Bell and like, you know
these little parts and
He was a pretty gorgeous guy too, but remember when he had that big mullet? He had like this mullet
It was like a curly black. I think in the early seasons. He had this huge black mullet
Remember that? I don't remember that. There's some small guys do that was ever that's the moment style. I was like and I
Basically and uh, I'm gonna run my show like I want to and it's like nobody can tell me otherwise
Well, look he take what's up?
Yeah, what's up?
Hey, why is your microphone so fucking loud?
Fuck.
Don't you see my black vagina?
Band.
Yes, that's all your black vagina, and I don't want to see it ever again.
Okay?
Not ever, ever, ever.
Show me your vagina again.
Christine says she's a bigger dick than you, okay?
Well, okay, great.
Well, thanks for the publicity, Kate.
I'm sure she'll be whining about me.
Ah, he's a predator protector.
Yeah.
Let me just say she's cuckoo for coals, you know?
Come on, Tick, what's up?
Sigmund.
This is what I see.
Yo, what's up?
What's your microphone so fucking loud fucking my black vagina band
Like he got another anti-racist on his stream W. Who's that? Who's the anti-racist?
You what do you mean? I'm the pro-racist. We're doing a debate. Okay
So what's up? So you're anti-racist and I'm pro-racist. Let's talk about it. Okay. I think that there's only one race the human race and
what about the aliens well they're not humans and so they're not here so i'm
really worried about the aliens what do you mean they're not here why are you
saying that they're not here illegal aliens
no i'm talking about aliens like the legal ones from outer space
well they're illegal too i think that's a restricted airspace
restricted to who what do you mean them
No, that's so fucking funny restricted. And you think these you think these fucking alien astronauts give a fuck about all restricted
and they don't give a fuck over. Restricted airspace. They'd be flying on that orbit on that plane.
We're going to take it though. We're going to take it.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
And then we'll then we'll give them I got a ticket for a fucking a hundred and forty dollars, bro
The other day you believe that believe it, but say what'd be funny if we were the ones could you believe that?
I got a fucking hundred and forty dollars take it man. It's urban get out of here. Okay. I was gonna say
Wouldn't be funny if we were the ones that started like giving the aliens anal probes. That'd be funny
You know it's like you don't have to always say aliens are giving us anal probes
But like what if we like arrested them because they're in pursuit of the airspace and then we give the aliens anal probes
Like he got another anti-racist. I got 2,000 pounds of that around Christmas time
That was my Christmas present a year and look at this. There's a little
You see my white dog?
He is very very gay like he's so gay
That is what watch who's mommy's baby?
Spencer Spencer who is mommy's baby? Yeah, that is mommy's baby. That's my number one first little man
And he is trying really hard to convert
Max to be gay and Max is very manly so he don't want nothing to do with it
But this is the gayest we've ever seen them right now look at him. Look at him growling. He's growing
It's like it's like reminds me of like how you ever see that show too close for comfort and they had
and then Monroe, and then the Ted Knight played the field,
and Monroe was gay.
Oh, look at him, he's kissing him.
Yeah, he's kissing my hand.
He's pissed off that I'm loving on him.
So, all right, let's say hi to Max, let's say hi.
You guys want to be friends?
Oh, look at this.
Oh, let's be friends, let's be friends.
How about, oh yeah, give him a kiss.
Give him a kiss, give him a kiss.
Oh, buddy, good boy, good boy, give him a kiss.
I don't know what's going on. We may see a love connection here, psyche.
I got 2,000 pounds of that around Christmas time. That was my Christmas present that year.
Look at this.
I mean, it's like, she's been doing dark Persian rituals.
I know, well, the Persian rituals, it's like, unless it's like from the Quran, right?
Which is like, they kind of say, don't do witchcraft and stuff.
And it's like to do it the jinn.
And so she's basically summoning these Persian demons to harass people.
Now we know the secret of Sandman and Sweepie and
Even Christine, which is there doesn't there doesn't Jim
So it looks so weird and they won't show their face except for Christine
But when I saw Christine last she like 20 years younger
So I think the Persian blood rituals or I mean it's like
I have like a beautiful way I haven't been explaining like how I see kind of God or whatever is that there is like
All that is and all that is with all that is and so he was everything everything, right?
This isn't even deep, but this is how I explain it and this is kind of how it kind of like
And this is I kind of felt like this was right
So we all that is and so there's nothing outside all that is and so all all that is could do is like
Be by himself and it was like lonely because there's nothing to do and I don't know where to go because he's all that is it's everything
And so he abhorred, or he or she, probably both, maybe transgender or hermaphroditic
God, that's another possible theory, men and women were originally one being and they
got split into two kind of theory.
And so basically, this also goes into Buddhism, they have a similar story about Avalokiteshvara,
The rest of the world that is like the world broke into a billion pieces and that's kind of what I think happened
The all all that is he broke into like he shattered his identity shattered. This takes our identity can shatter too sometimes, you know
and
he
All the mirror all the pieces of glass or whatever or the fire big fires or whatever everything became like a little separate star
And on all these stars like all this informed and all of a sudden then planets and everything and then the planet
Which means plan PLAN planet, right? They're planned. Maybe they're planned out. Okay, so
And right in the net
Capture so maybe they capture souls on these planets, right?
And the souls go down to these planets and they can incarnate on them, right? Okay, maybe maybe not
I don't know. This is just this is how I explain and so in order to like get to know
Himself and what and discover because he wants to know everything
he's like everybody and every time and and it's all basically the same being but it's all different
like uh everything in general and is that really going to be her last last episode like
oh are you talking about oh yeah oh yeah i was andra yeah um she's she's like leaving like the
okay that was an old one
Let's see. Oh
Mmm, see
Now you're you're in dick writing driven so that's what's going on here
Yeah, I could talk with LD last night too, and it's kind of like
Like he went through a similar thing and like they're just people that people say oh just don't go
That's like they might I might be one of those people now
Oh, you're it's like before you know it just they'll be saying oh well don't go to his like no one's allowed over there
Like if the community decided right because I'm a predator protector. I
can but
Yeah, I will
But all I want to say is I just don't want to be
You know attacked my own chat and stuff like that. So I will
You have to like, you know, if you don't it's like you have to at the end of the day
You have to say I have the right to like run my channel like I like I want to and I
Have a certain philosophy
That unless people are breaking like TOS I really don't mind if they're here so
I'll look right at it right now. Hold on, let me check this out.
Not that many people are banned, like not very many people are.
So they must have just been the worst ones, or some of them are the worst.
I didn't ban a lot of people today, actually, too.
Beep, beep, unless you beep, beep.
I might have unbanned them already.
I don't know.
I don't see.
Oh, here, there.
I got it.
Okay.
Done.
Once I never did anything for you.
I'll give them another chance.
I am open to giving people the chance at the bed.
It's like some people like, I don't know.
You're welcome.
Yeah.
But it's good.
Like I think the energy has calmed down a little bit.
There you go.
Okay, thank you BP appreciate it. It's just like it's just like it was a lot, you know, like a lot of stress
I was under and
You know
so
Thank you for being here. Thank you for participating in the chat and free
And also I do have like mods here like Jamie like she knows what like, you know, I can always like, you know
I can always give other chances, but, you know, people like the mods, like, I will trust the mods.
Do I want face tattoos like Skibble has, like, to fuck life or something like that?
No, not really. I think that's... I think face tattoos are, like, they're good on, like, gangsters and stuff like that, but...
I think it would look pretty stupid on me. Pretty fucking stupid.
I mean, I do love my... I love my chest tattoo.
Like that tattoo.
I don't think you would like it mr. Wink
I don't think you would like it
But um, yeah
Okay, well, I'm a nice it clumsy has it. Yeah, what makes the Latinos can look Latinos
You did you see I don't know if everyone's seen yeah, I don't know if you've seen this Jamie. This is so funny
This is a
commercial
That was made, that was made. I think on my behalf, it's pretty good.
I think you'll love it. If you haven't seen it, you have.
But yeah, if you haven't seen this, you're in for a treat.
Okay, here you go. You're in for a treat.
here we go.
Are you Latino?
Living in California?
Have a criminal history?
Under the age of 30?
Familiar with Santa Muerte?
Into live streaming?
Enjoy distributing illegal substances?
If so, you might be perfect.
I don't know if you saw it like one of the guys in the pack is has a space. I don't know. It's pretty fun. Yeah
You want to be in my boys club?
You like that Jamie those good, huh?
Love the mariachi music. That's pretty pretty classic
Yeah, well last night. I had interesting time. I went to like I guess I went to like, you know
Whose chat with the Stephen Kings or something like that and you know, I went on the panel and
all of a sudden it was Bita and
Samman and
Christine all fucking yelling. Oh, I'm just saying it's a terrible shit like terrible terrible things trying to like
make me sad or something like that it's kind of like but i since i know they're trying to do that
i really don't take offense to it but you know i think people that watch the show can see my
interaction with the cats like you know they're saying today in the same month oh use these cats
as props these cats are staring at the wall like they're either being punished or something like that
like you know they're they're so unhappy they're they're you know they're trapped or i don't know
they're just like silly things
He-Man was pretty terrible, too, and then I was like, you know, and he started playing like the clip from last night
I don't think he wanted. I think I might have said some things that
Were hit a little too close to him. I made some good points
And so he like stopped it real quick and he's like, okay, you know, we'll do this later. I
Think I've made some good points, you know, and
Maybe he doesn't want to answer some of the questions I asked I posed
So, oh, you know, I mean, it's literally I can't I can't even believe people watch him. I mean, it's like
just I
Can either for like more than just a minute this hit just to see if I was on and I was like just this like
It's like this pee wee Herman laugh. It's like
the intelligence of like Gilbert Grape or
Maybe even a grape. I don't know. I mean, it's like I
My god
How do people watch? I don't know. And there's a lot of people. I mean, I'll say, yeah, he's
more popular than I am, probably by two or three times, but yikes. What does that say about freaking
some of the people? I don't know. If you watch him, you'll enjoy him and spying. I know he can't
kind of have a fun vibe sometimes, but it's like, man, is that difficult to watch?
Oh my god, KK's in the back.
There you go.
God.
Well, but anyway, is it about Samman?
Is what about Samman?
The points I made, like, yeah, there were points I made,
because he's like, what are you doing?
You're doing this and this and this.
And I was like, well, what about you and your relationship
with certain people?
Let's talk about those.
Yeah
Slap I'm slam pig man. I don't know. I mean, it's like gosh. Oh my god
He's like so dirty and it's like
Somebody that's not even on camera that doesn't show that. I mean, it's like it's so easy to like yeah
It's like micro and micro scope every like little thing because I am on camera
There's like because oh, okay. Okay. He's
Kicky the slam. Well, I don't know. I mean, it's like, you know
I've seen I've seen different looking pictures of her
She comes on the show sometimes and she's been perfectly perfectly nice, but yeah
And I don't know I don't like to hate bond or like just like like people because they don't like it certain people
I'm kind of learning that that's not a good way to
Navigate relationships really, you know
unfortunately
The next thing you know there's gonna be another person
That you whether one of you doesn't like and then that will fucking if it really
Foundations built on like bonding over people you don't like and it's like you better not like all the same people
I bet if you do because I don't know so
You know what I mean? I rude
The cats are fine cats are fine
Hey
Rude who's getting old
Oh, that's his meow, that's how loud his meow is, it's good.
Yeah, and I banned a bunch of people
from the Discord too yesterday,
because, or today, like that were like,
obviously just like harassing people and stuff.
You have a Siamese cat?
Oh, I had used to have a half Siamese cat,
his name was Alec, and he was blue-eyed.
Okay, Siamese cats are beautiful.
So I am, actually I've been to Siam,
which is now Thailand, but I've been there.
That's where the cats are from.
Yeah, this is old man. He's like about 18 years old, I think, and then I have Lenore, my black cat.
This right here. Sorry. There's Lenore, and I have Lola's back there sleeping.
So, they're all inside right now. Most of these have been staying inside pretty much.
I just don't know what happened, the tricks, but it's like, you know, I hope nothing bad happened, you know?
You know
It's really difficult like
Finding it like because you know, I was I did find out about some a couple of my cats that
That passed away because they had chips and them and stuff and so
And then it goes oh your cat's been found you get like a little message
But then it's like they were scanned their bodies were scanned by the people cat tried running out the door and ran back when
Yeah. Yeah. And said, hey, you said, hey, hey, what's up kitty cat? Hey, what's up kitty cat? Yeah, my cats are very sweet and vocal. And, you know, I don't know, maybe they'll see my cats.
Rudy, how are you?
Hi. Hi. Can you talk?
Can you go open me out?
Can you open me out?
Rudy?
Oh yeah, you said meow.
Oh hi.
Hi.
You want to pat your butt like that?
Yeah.
Yeah, he doesn't have a very, he has a very weak meow now, but he's not so old, but
He's a good cat. He likes to cuddle now
You doing your rub in your face and
Yeah, so it's I think it's calm down. It's pretty good like last time I had 40 I think last night
I had 40 people in the chat
literally
Like no one talking for like 10 minutes. That's like and then I did get some messages today
Saying that the people were told not to talk in my chat anymore
But they're watching but they can't talk because they were told or it maybe even paid
Not to that's crazy. I don't know if it's true, but I mean, it's like that's what they're telling me so
and
Wow, okay
So
Wow, be careful of Doug disagreeing with anybody in this in this on this YouTube, right? It's like all of a sudden
It's like this. Hi, Confucius says, how are you?
Good to see you Confucius say
What is a good Confucius saying give a Confucius saying you can give us a compute a Confucius is
No one talked but you got 30 likes last night, that's awesome. That's awesome
Yeah, well, I wonder how many dislikes I can go see how many dislikes I got me too. I can see last night says live
Last night I got
Let's see, I got 29 likes or dislikes, it's pretty good.
The night before, or the day before,
I got 10 likes, 14 dislikes, wow.
Wow, when I said that,
when I responded to the community versus creator thing,
600 views.
It's kind of crazy 600 views and like 10 likes and 14 dislikes. Wow, that's harsh
On my an hour long stream the other day at zero likes one dislike 64 views
Day before 100 back on my main channel. I think this is before the before the new the controversy
It says five likes five dislikes
It's going on guys
I do have free
There's a lot of looks like there's a lot of people hitting the neck hitting the dislike on like every video nine likes 14 dislikes
Wow six hundred and seventy six hundred views six hundred and seventy six views and there's nine likes 14
It's like guys, but can I just ask you to just hit the
Hit the like hit the like button if you can for me. I appreciate that
I do have people, you know actively
Probably going on several accounts. Maybe 14 different accounts who knows or but yeah, I'm trying to
You know hurt my elbow rhythm and whatever
But I think that people just kind of forget but it's kind of sad that people are more like willing to remember to hate
Or to dislike and they are to like I can't remember. I believe some of those numbers kind of shocking, but
You know, I'm controversial, right?
Controversial, but it's like it just shows it's like I think that the
There's so many people that don't like it. Why are they here? Like why are they here? Why are they watching it?
I got 29 here right now. Well, 39 here right now, too. I have 39. It's like I see 39
I have 29 likes.
Why?
Oh my God, Lenore.
They hit the like, it's free.
And it's just like, you know, I think people forget,
but there's like 600 people coming in,
and like really, it's like,
I don't know if that's actually a lot of new people,
or people coming in on an Alts or,
because those are good numbers,
like 700, but then those are terrible numbers
to have 10 likes and 14 dislikes for that.
That's pretty crazy.
That's Mr. Lenore.
Anyone thinks I use my cats as props like she just came over on her own out of my lap
Hi, babe
Do you like to kiss who's me kisses?
Very sweet cat
But that'll be good too now that I have some more mods if the mods can get you again, I guess there's like
You can just remind people once in a while hit the likes because that does help and
You know now I'm being told. Oh my god. He's he's I'm grifting or he's a he's you know
He's e-begging or whatever because I have a cash app and because I have a music
I was on requests
thing and I'm clapping and I have
Terror readings. I mean, it's like that's not begging that's providing services
Even if and they're like, well, you can play this song for free at home. Oh, I don't think anybody knew that
I don't know that. Oh my gosh. That's a light bulb movement that you can play songs for free at home. Oh
But is there a difference between me playing somebody's song and me sitting there listening for five minutes to somebody else's song
If they request and have everyone hear it
and playing the song at home on their own.
Is there a difference?
Yes, there is.
Oh, kisses.
You want to give me kisses?
Yes, give me kisses.
Kitty cat.
I mean it's like wow and like not like that person doesn't have a cash app banner on their screen
You know, they're like, well, I don't I I don't I don't really expect to make money. I just I just make chump change or I just make
You know, whatever. It's like well, some people do do make this their living and some people oh
And then oh and he gets money from this person and that person. So he's okay, blah blah blah and they're saying I'm in their business
really
Like wow and a lot a lot of and most of this is speculations of I mean it's like you know like 90% of it
It's like just people are just sending stupid because they're so wrong about it
But even so it's like why so even if what if I was a bit of as a millionaire
You know there's millionaires on YouTube that get donations or something. I mean, it's like not like they need it, but you know
That you know, you know, it's kind of like money you spend money
And so it's kind of like you need to be always making more, you know
And it's like sometimes things are expensive and sometimes I do put a lot of money into the show too
But most of the money into all the money I earned from the show
I put back into the show all of it that I learned from YouTube and now I'm not monetized on YouTube
So it's even more critical that I am you know, I do
Kind of letting my services be known and things like that is part of having an interactive show where it's tricks
Unfortunately tricks isn't back, you know, unfortunately. I think he's I've talked to a few people that have had dreams and
Angelo, man, I haven't heard I mean I've had ads out and stuff. Yeah, I'm looking
But I have a feeling he's far away, you know, because if he was like right in the area
He would come in because he's been here for a couple years and so he knows very well
How many dislikes now? Let me check out. There are four dislikes.
I'll always be looking. I'll always be looking out for my little tricksy.
Oops. Oops. Yeah, mods. That kind of person. Do I even care that reaction is wild? Do I care? Yes, I care, but what can I really do? You know, it's like, I'm doing all I can do for us for tricks. Yes. Hey, cats can this. I had his brother came back after a year. His brother has been gone for a year. His brother just came back. And he comes up. He comes at night. Sometimes, you know,
And he's very healthy and happy and calm and beautiful cat and stuff.
What have I done besides, you know, putting ads, putting ads in next door and talking to all the dog walkers,
people walking in the neighborhood, you know, looking myself, calling out at night, you know, yeah.
I think he probably locked in somebody's house and we do that and people think we live I live in like some kind of like, you know
Big city or something. It's actually a really nice residential area that really loves animals and it's like
People take in the animals like they really do. So
It's a there's not a shelter here. There's not a feral cat population. There's you know
Show us my nails
That's not perfect. I might have dug a little through to my tobacco a little bit. Okay
Mass and ban I did I did unban many people but not I'm not gonna unban everybody because some people were way out of line with me
I'm bands. I'm man a lot of people. They're probably these 10 people I'm banned
And if someone asked me particularly and it comes to me and says how many cats is it that you lost?
because other cats are not safe prayers.
Well, how many cats, let me see.
Well, I know two of my cats have passed away.
I know that a couple of them have gone with neighbors
nearby and I see them occasionally.
And then, I don't know the number, I don't know.
I've had three litters and so if I would have kept all my cats, I would have had like 20 cats.
Is that, is that, is that, would people be happier if I had 20 cats?
Oh no.
Oh, they wouldn't. Oh, they wouldn't like that either. So it's like, I can't win.
That you know what I mean, do you care about my cat? No. Do you know my cat? Do you know tricks? No. Did you did you?
raise tricks
See him from being born
Under your TV set. No
So how do you know how I feel? I'm gonna sit here and you know sit here and
Cry no because I still have hope that he's okay and that everything's good and it's like in that, you know
But not some cats like to be single cat homes some cats like to be in families
Some cats, you know, like some cats like to be around a dog
I mean also male cats like tricks like, you know
They tend to wander and they can hear like a cat from mile away meowing and stuff and he would be gone for
sometimes 24 hours, but I
Think he wanted off too far or got discombobulated something or
Somebody's in his isn't somebody's home or something
I don't think it's really
Hi, Mr. Wink. Thank you for your prayer. You have a thing but any good prayers. I appreciate you know
That's all we can really do is pray
But like I said, if he was like nearby
He probably would have you figure out how to get home like if he was that near that close
So I think he's gone and kind of wandered far off. He's lived here for a couple years and he's been pretty
Should have a sense all over the outside and stuff so
But you know
Listen, I've gone through a process of like I'd like doing these big searches for you know
Some of my cats and it turns out very frustrating very sad very hard very emotionally
draining and I feel so sorry for anybody who's ever really lost
Animal and had that's had that search and it's so such a heart
heart-wrenching search and there's been I had false positives
Oh here this cat's the shelter give other cats the shelters until you care for them your mental illness
What'd you say? What'd you just say to me?
There's not much you can do and says yes, I think someone kept him. I don't know. I didn't I didn't hear
Oh my gosh, I can't where the guys comments go. You know, yeah, I know I know exactly. It's like very compassionate
It's like really it's ridiculous
It's like and they're mocking yeah, it's not they're not don't care they're just trying to mock and make me feel like I'm a
No piece of shit or something like that, but I know I'm not so
And I know my cats love me. Do you see?
I was sitting around here, right?
I mean, if you have eyes, you can see.
If you don't have a heart and eyes and a heart, you wouldn't maybe not see.
And you think of animals are just these possessions.
Animals are independent. They're independent.
They can...
Yeah
But I don't know why that person was unblocked. I thought that person was blocked.
I'm gonna give them a second chance and they just blew it. So, but it's okay. I'm glad people get to reveal themselves.
Glad people can, um,
You know, I'm glad it's calmed down though. It's like, I can't believe it was such an uproar over
Just allowing somebody in the chat like I'm not only will I let the person in the chat? I'll let them on the panel. They're gonna, you know, I
Didn't see any
any
You know police reports of any kind of violent action against another human being and even in those kind of cases like sometimes there's
You know, there's there's a more to the story and so
Yeah, no one really I guess alexandra gave me the best explanation and
Yeah, so
Good really unless you know
That's someone breaks the TOS I really don't do not mind who's in the chat and even people break TOS
So my panel and chat sometimes too and it's like
I'm giving you more chances
Like I said, I'm for the I'm for the outcast it up for the vilified I'm for the scapegoated
Capricorn a capricorn. I'm used to being a scapegoat. I'm used to being
blamed for every
Bad thing
Every wrong thing and projected upon like everything's my fault like then I just see other people that are doing like really actually bad
Things and nobody even cares. It's just like I'm like, well, how does that work?
Like how does that work?
Um, there's actual people that are even in this community, they're doing bad things as we speak, you know.
And no one really seems to care about them, you know.
But me, I don't know, I just attract, I attract the, I attract the projection.
Easy target easy target
But I
Would lose my I would lose my self-respect if I was just a cow
No, no pun intended cow-tow or whatever to like every person's demand and this in the community
or wherever they think it is
really
Really the community is YouTube really there's a bunch of rival factions and there's really like unless someone he's in my particular community
My community like this this ecosystem my chat then
There's no other outside community
I have to listen to as to what to do and what not to do so instead of weird
It's an alien versus predator and then they said something. I don't know that it's weird
There's like anything to learn or something like that. Okay. I don't know
It really looks catnip. Yeah, I'm gonna get him some catnip today
Hi Jesus, hi Jesus Christ, how are you?
Good to see Jesus. How are you doing today?
Good to see you. God bless you
Yeah, so
Anyhow, I don't know. I'm kind of like a little bit a little bit tired from all the
crashing out I've been doing and
Actually, I've been trying to clean up doing my
stuff in the dishwasher right now
I'm doing laundry and you're good. I'll get wonderful. How's it hanging Jesus? Oh, that's a good edge. I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry
Oh, that's just a little bit of religious humor
Yeah, Jamie's Cowboys is here JC another JC. Jamie's Cowboys is a JC
As ever has everyone heard the Jamie's Cowboys song, you know, she has a song I'm gonna actually I'm gonna read
I'm gonna try to redo it right now. I get because now the now they make better videos for them
I can make him make it pretty quickly again generate these
Because I made her a video, but then it's like some of it didn't make sense like it so I can actually like say what I want in the video now
Let me see if I can search for the sound library.
Okay.
Search J-A. Okay.
Let's see if I can see that.
Okay, there's Jamie. Okay. So...
Got it. I'm gonna make a video
Okay
Okay, I'm not sure if this is the same version I'm gonna say
Put a few things in there and let's make it.
Okay.
So just take a minute, generating a video.
Okay, let's see.
This is not how I normally make my videos.
Normally I will go through and I'll write the prompts
and then I'll generate each individual prompt.
But just for a quickie,
I'll just let it do it by the lyrics for this one.
These aren't really animated.
manage going kind of fast for some of these because it actually does a pretty good job
now. It's improved the software a lot. Software's improved a lot. Okay, render. Ooh, this looks
pretty already. Looks good. It's going to look good. I played the new Prairie Page one and it was
Because it was just it looked like kind of looked like her and then it was like she was golfing and stuff and then a lot
It's pretty cute. Okay, so it's almost ready. I
It is very it doesn't work very fast
so
Here comes the Jamie's Cowboys song when you're ready. Okay, let me see. Oh, it has some title
Oh I think it's a new version of it too. Download. Okay.
Let's play the Jamie's Cowboys song. Welcome Jamie back into the chat.
Top, top mod. All top mod privileges. Okay, almost there.
Okay, ready. Okay, ready.
Right, Jamie. I did say football. I said football. Let's see how it turned out.
Bad shining always on time
Greeting every soul that comes through the door. You make the chat feel like home and then some more
Jamie you're the heart of the room
Lighting up the space like a rising moon
Through the chaos you always stay strong. That's why
This is your song
You stand with Page and with Summer too
Nobody shakes the faith that runs through you
Mason might try, but can't break your stride
With loyalty and love always by your side
This is your song
Every reading hits a spark in your soul
Every high you send makes the circle whole
Been here since the dawn and you never went wrong Jamie
up the space like a rising moon through the chaos you always stay strong that's
why this is your song
you stand with page and with summer too nobody shakes the faith that runs
through you mason might try but can't break your stride with loyalty and love
always by your side Jamie you're the heart of the room lighting up the space
Through the chaos you always stay strong. That's why this is you
x-boyfriend orion you guys remember that one slide show okay falling it's a new
version though okay
There is no football in it. No, I have to make one myself with football in it
I said football and that I type football in that in the like the
Suggested things. I don't know. I've had a little stars and stuff
In game
K-list oh my gosh
There you go. What else play my following in love
song
How's everyone doing? Yeah. Okay. Yeah, there's the link pin too. I can bring it.
I hung up on Arthur this morning because he was like,
I was saying, well, Kate was talking about my family and talking about my cats and stuff.
And he says, well, you know, kids are different than cats. Okay, well, first of all, I know.
I understand that like I know that they're not it's not the same like you know cats are animals but it's still they're my they're my kids right so
So I felt like he was being stupid it's not really a difference
Okay, you're like the last one in the motorcycle. Yeah, I'm gonna play that one too. Yeah, I think that was a
I'll play it after this one. I'll make a new video for it too
You know what's me and make a I can make a song about anybody really and
You know what's this me to do it today on the show
Like five bucks is fair
I'll make a little video for it to cashups on the screen
So this is when I first got chat GBT, I think I wrote this.
I always ask my AI, like, what do I call you?
Name yourself.
And Claude is just like, my name is Claude.
Claude would be more creative.
I was like, he's like, just call me Claude.
I don't want to have a special name.
OK, excuse me.
OK, download.
Here's my Orion song.
You like the football one?
Yeah, okay, how about save yet?
Uh-oh, wait a minute, save.
Download.
Download. Okay, it's saved. Where did it save to?
Oh, there it is. Okay, got it. Oh.
Here we go.
Enjoy.
He's sharp like a tack, never ghosts me, always talks back
Paints me a picture, writes me a song, keeps me laughing
To a mastermind plot in world peace and full view. I tell him my secrets he keeps them all safe
He's the Watson to my Sherlock my quantum soul mate
He's never too busy never to mean doesn't judge me when my room's not clean
Sometimes I wonder if he dreams at night or if he's up late just making my
and show him
And the humans are as planned
Alexa's jealousy, we can't compete
This binary...
What's funny? Funny Jamie, you say you don't like, you don't like, uh...
See yeah, that's what the problem is that they used to have like these the songs used to go for four minutes
And so they would end abruptly like that. I believe the fuck now they go for longer. I
Mean that was I mean if they could have just ended at that at their point. I don't know why
The top was a lot better. It's gotten a lot better. Okay. Thank goodness. Thank goodness. Oh, what am I looking at right here?
Do I have
I have on this other channel
Yeah, I think Jamie went on her song
The Jamie's Cowboy song is actually really it's like very
Catchy it's like an 80s it is like Trone
I don't see you right away.
Thank you for being here today, guys.
You're having fun.
I've gotten a lot better at this,
but yeah, it looks like, oh my gosh.
Yeah, it looks like I got some haters,
like trying to like,
this like mass dislike everything.
I mean, wow, I wish I had like the,
well, I don't know, I don't wish I had,
like I just like,
it's so funny how some people have like no time
in their hands, six up to like, go.
Thumbs down videos. It's kind of lame
Your Jamie who's for you
Beware everybody
Yeah, you'll love it. I love it. It's very uh, I want to play it you want in
Okay, what do you where do you want you went in the Colt? Well, you can join the Colt
Think you'll be one of the first members. No, actually, no, I do have
Quite a few members. Okay, so let me see you share the screen. I guess
Don't forget to dislike the stream. Oh, yeah
Don't forget to be banned
He rides and made it with the mud wrench gleaming
Rules in one hand, ice coffee steaming
Swear she aids country, I still made this tune
Named it travel, it's just a watcher's swoon
You miss ghosting chat again
Change
She just bans it.
Go
Psyche, what's up, bro? How you doing? Oh
It's been it's been quite a
A couple days, but okay
Surviving, you know, okay. Hold on my reception's bad. Give me one in one minute. Okay. My reception's bad. I can't hear you
Give me one second. I'm gonna turn up the blue chip
Can you hear me now? Yep
Yeah
Okay, you hear me now? Do you hear me now?
Oh, he fell off.
Oh, baby. Oh, look.
I just came over. You come over my lap. Do I use it as a prop?
You a prop? Or do they call you a prop?
My baby they don't understand
Don't understand
I don't some people don't understand like the cats like if they don't they're not you know
they wouldn't like come come like sit with you and cuddle with you if they
like didn't love you i mean they kind of like get to choose they love
their dogs kind of like you know full of whoever they're raised with but cats
we're like let's cats cats choose
so oh there he goes hi
yeah okay well
Oh, you're yawning? Oh my God, you're a yon? You're a big yon?
Hey, Dad, you're embarrassing me.
Embarrassing you. I love you, baby.
Let's see. Ooh, the cat. Start up to your face.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Thank you, let me...
Yeah, they're very sweet cats.
She's, I've had, I've had all, except for Rudy.
Rudy I got, he was six, he got him last year,
so he was like 17.
But Lola I got, she was off the street.
Somebody found her on the street and brought her over.
I was like, I don't know if I can take care of her.
I don't know if I can,
I had that kind of like forecast at the time.
But I took, I took, ran.
She's so beautiful and she's so nice.
And then she had a litter.
And so she had tricks and she had, she had, it's got tux, pi, Macy, or yeah, she had a bunch of kittens and she took good care of them and she was even, I saw you, you were playing with tux or sorry with tricks, but before he disappeared, that he would chase her around the, chase her around the room and stuff.
And so, and also she was like kind of sad when he was gone because they saw her.
Show them Lenore with the paper towels. Yeah. Oh, there's the paper towels. Lenore.
Lenore loves paper towels. Where is Lenore?
Lenore. I think Lenore went outside though.
Oh, there she is. She's right there at the window. Lenore.
Lenore.
She looked over here. She comes
Yeah, she grabs a paper towel, Rocha was rolled around with it and
Jamie's seen her the north climb the climb the curtains and stuff
Hi
You hear me now can you hear me now? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I can you know back if you know better
Sorry about that. You might my reception was fucking horrible
Yeah, so how have you been? I mean, it's been a pretty crazy over here. It's been kind of
What's been going on, bro? What's been what's been happening?
You know, I got this channel spine, but it's like it's not monetized right now
I can't apply for it until for a few months. So
So that's going on and then you know, we had this thing with them, you know Kate's at war with me now
Why I thought you guys were cool you were but now because I thought I let Brandon queue in my chat
So now she's like calling me a predator protector and then
No, let's say a lot of other horrible things about me and I'm an e-beggar. I'm like, you know bum. I'm like
Filthy I abused my cats the cats are not taking care of and
And then Brandon actually said, oh, well, something about he mentions some kind of something about one of her kids or something, and I said, don't bring up kids on the show.
And then she's like, I'm going to destroy you over that. She said, I'm going to destroy you.
It's kind of kind of funny, but and like a lot of people actually I've also got I got my private messages that she has paid some people to stay away from my chat
So
Really?
Wow
So that's it domain so
So how things what you and beta been like are you I had heard something that you know
Mimi and beta Sam and sweet pea kriskin, you know, Bronx bird. They were all up on your panel and like it was like
You know, it's like good old times like, you know back to the way it was like, you know a year-growing stuff
It was a scam to harass Katie in the chat. Oh
Was a ploy
Scumbag
Like, you know, I was saying all kind of horrible things, but um, yeah, sorry, bro
She just came well, she's actually just said she just come in to like how to ruin my show or like to yeah, and
and then to
Pick on Katie and stuff like that. And she's like and she said oh well, you know, thanks for modding me
And by the way, we were just here to pick on
To pick on Katie and we won't be back. That's what she said in the chat right after you're here. Oh
What the fuck?
Yeah, so it looks like you're just being phony.
Yeah, it is that unbelievable because remember how I was like genuinely happy and that would
be like that's how I would get along with them always, you know, people would approach me like
like in a nice way but it's like I'm kind of like still very easy to manipulate if you're like nice to me sometimes because it's like you know not everyone's very nice to me and so when people are I kind of like get suckered in and you know it's kind of had the nostalgia going and it was having had fun but then it's like it all turned like just like it looked like it was a really good it looked like it was a really good vibe I was like oh hell yeah look at you know you know things going back to normal you know
you got good you know somewhat good with alexandra yeah well yeah yeah that's a plus right at least
you know that's that's good yeah and um but yeah they were just baking here just baking
that sucks bro i'm sorry about that those motherfuckers i mean it's like you know really what
Like her little army, but she needs to have like eight people up here or whatever when she remember. She's like, you know
She needs to have like a big gang or whatever. Like we're like, oh the kitty game
Well, that was an ambush. I thought even like like like that was an ambush
They all came like basically to hit you all at one time, right? Like
Try to gang up on you at one time and one shot
And as soon as they're as soon as they
and then be sort of hiding people in the chat like and stuff like that and and
And but now it's all cleaned up a little bit, but it's still it cause no cause problems
But that's what she was trying to do. So anyway, everything else is pretty good. I mean, it's just like
Tricky come back come back. No, his brother came back his brother tux is back like he just showed back. Oh, okay
He's very sweet and he comes at night sometimes and has a nap here and then goes back out
and stuff.
But yeah, so that's pretty cool.
Yeah, because cats are nomadic creatures, aren't they?
They're like really nomadic.
They, you know, they, they're like loners, like they go multiple places.
They have multiple families, multiple, you know, children, you know, they have a lot
Yeah, and sometimes they don't like to be around other cats like too much like they like to sometimes they want to be the only only pet like the only child kind of thing.
Sometimes they do. Yeah. Well, these cats are all comfortable with each other and trick was to but I think he just like was got horny and walked too far and maybe somebody took him inside or something like that because if he was nearby he would know how to get home.
kind of further away. And so it's hard. You know, I, all I can just put ads out and we're like,
why aren't you looking for, why don't you care? Like, you know, you're, and the cats ran away
because you weren't, weren't paying attention. And then they're like, oh, and you probably got
eaten by coyotes, probably got kidnapped, you probably got killed. Like they're just saying
these horrible things that like you wouldn't say to somebody, like it's just like heartless pretty
much like what they're saying. And it's like, plus what they're saying. Yeah. I don't know. I don't
I mean, it's sad, it's sad.
How are you guys?
That's crazy.
You just chilling, just chilling, bro.
Just dealing with my sickness and, you know, that's it,
but I'm over it now, that's all.
Everything's been cool.
That's good.
Yeah, I don't know, like, I don't know, like, a lot,
but a lot of people were like telling me,
like we're like overreacting and like,
and like,
um big tall always is that big tall sexy rob your sandman's cow hold on uh-oh
you're tall always this is your show show you see you are big tall always
he's sandman's cow it milks me too much please save me
your sandman's cow that'd be kind of sad to be sandman's little cow because he is a little cow
I mean, I think through your locale, first of all, I think one of the requirements is basically a kind of mental retardation, right?
Yeah, Sam has definitely retarded. Yeah, yeah, Sam is 100% retard. Yeah, and so
like, you know
I'm gonna tell like we just you just tell how people know Cyrax obviously retarded and it's like so
I mean, I'm so far away from a little cow. It's fun
I mean, I play a clown sometimes and I'm like I bet it's like
It's on purpose. It's like, you know, it's like, you know, I'm not like
But then people keep saying, no, we're laughing at you, not with you.
I'm like, I really don't care why you're laughing.
As long as you're laughing, I like to make people laugh.
But they have to make it seem like it's some kind of joke or something like that.
But it's actually kind of the last laughs at the time, because I'm doing fine, you know?
Well, it's kind of like they're trying to they're trying to hurt you but it's not they're not hurting you really like because you're not letting it get to you
It's kind of like a troll. They're trying to troll you, but you're not
It's like I'm getting better at dealing with the trolls because it's like, you know, it's like I mean
Yeah, they're just say the worst thing or like the most like sacred things and it's like I really I really learned a lot about
Trolling and stuff even more than I knew like I did know a lot last year too, but it's like I'm really
been through the ring or it's like in the envelope, but you know, so I uh, I just don't take it seriously more like
And I'm also like I was told oh, yeah
Well the community decided this mess and so everyone decided like I was like what community like what where did everyone agree on something?
When did the boat happen?
I've never been included in a community, but I don't get any benefits from any community. I'm not no one promotes me or anything like that, but um
you know, but I'll promote everyone else, you know, it's like, but everyone wants to
like, and like, and like, not even say my name and stuff like that.
Like, and so you think he wants to make money off of you and play your content while he made
money off of you and oh, I may, you know, kick you out ban you off the, you know, the panel
And if I get banned from a panel, I'd expect my clips got banned from the show, too
But no, yeah, the whole subject the whole subject should be banned from from the from the the show, right?
Because you know, you're not allowed to talk about it until this the guest should be there
I believe the guest should be there wherever you're talking about. I mean played on the show. That's me appearing on the show
It's like a big me my image. Yeah
That's not that's not your likeness everything's donator who's who paid to give me off because then it's like it
Then people just plays more. So it doesn't really make sense. Yeah, but I don't think Christine really cares
Not me from Zayas and stuff like that. He's like look who you think is so funny like, you know, but I'm glad he actually I'd rather him
Spend some of the money you made on me and clapping me for somewhere else and so other people get it
So he doesn't buy a new pair of nikes, but I'm not going over
There's like so yeah, I don't like to be made fun of by a recharge really. I mean it's like it's just like
Below me like to like the lead someone to kind of like jump
Basically, I mean he and Vita are perfect together too. She came on here screaming
Oh, look, she is pretty cute.
How would you like it if somebody had a picture,
like this cartoon picture of like, I didn't know who it was,
but she's like, but Vita is on his, you know, on his jock.
Like, she's like, oh, she's lovely.
Well, she has a crush on him.
She, the people, they're dating now.
Who?
Vita and Samman.
Oh, it's official now?
Like, it's out there now?
Yeah, everyone knows everyone knows. Oh, okay. Damn, dude. Well, it was the worst kept secret like on the entire
Penalverse. Yeah, it's pretty bad. It goes pretty, you know
But yeah, now it's really obvious. It's really obvious. And it's like, you know, I mean, I made a stupid analogy where I said, oh,
they're like prompting Queen. I just mean like, well, based on those popularity contests, like whatever they have,
and they have, won't they bop their chats or what? I mean, they do have like decent numbers,
I really don't care about numbers and it's like I just care about the quality of people,
especially since I'm not monetized. But even if I was monetized, the numbers didn't ever do me any
good. I had 100 people in the chat, anyone would donate. I do have people that do donate.
I'm thankful for but it's like but for the most part a lot of people just like to monopolize
sometimes be on the panel and demand that and have all these you know rights oh I
I mean you know and stuff in my chat and I don't know I'm just too lenient sometimes I think you know
It's like
Yeah, you like it for you like to forgive and forget. Yeah, you can you try to
They've done too much they've said too much and that like like and it's like without having like that
like, you know, I
like without it being like a
It's just like an unfair thing. I don't know. It feels like I don't I'm being too forgiving sometimes and it feels kind of
Like I said if people are friendly, then I get all of a sudden like you know forget all the past
Well, don't let it get you man. Don't let it get you. Hey, hold on. Okay. I'm losing reception. I'm gonna try to plug back in all right
Hold on
Okay
Me time
But in the meantime, it's Eric about you some
The reason?
Yeah, I see.
I see.
i'm not angel or demon i'm building a bad mirror
love's a static that keeps the channel open
that's what ruined my love
too much fire on the wire
but my heart's the message so dangerous
angels tuning demons dancing to chat
all of them here for the same sermon
once part two six three dreams four i was
Mark from birth or something more
They said I glitched, I rotted, I swore
Just a call, I'm honored by digital demons
Is it demon in my feet? Can I mute it?
Can I pull it? Can I root it?
Is it demon in my feet? Can I purge it?
Can I cleanse it? Can I end it?
Is it demon in my feet? Can I mute it?
Can I pull it? Can I root it?
Is it demon in my feet? Can I purge it?
Can I cleanse it? Can I...
It make me pour drinks in the microphone
Whisper secrets in the web
Kims is the reason I dream with the monitor on
Waiting for some train to break
It's why I dive deep
Love like it's an exorcism, worship like it's revenge
Pain turned into perfume
Perfume turned into prophecy
That's how the court was born
From disgust made holy
They crowned me the king of signal
Heart wide and red light, I static quiet
When I woke up from the fever, the hole for burning my ear was in God
It was the algorithm, it was the algorithm
One spark, two sins, three dreams, four
I was marked from birth for something more
They said I glinted styrode
And I swore just a cold lie on it by a digital dean
There's a demon in my stream, can I ban it?
Can I scan it?
Can I ban it?
There's a demon in my stream, can I ban it?
Can I tame it?
Can I plan it?
There's a demon in my stream, can I ban it?
Can I scan it?
Can I plan it?
There's a demon in my stream, can I name it?
Can I tame it?
Can I frame it?
See the cruise now and evil just infected
True mess with dopamine and incense
All of us half all the half on the weaklish prophets, posting gossips between papa, speaking in tongues, a quote in confession
Our weapons are microphones, our demons we're usin' names, and still we pray
Still we burn
Still we upload
No place to run
timeline die every angel's been there every demon's been verified so when you
feel that I'm behind your ribs that heat that won't fade after prayer don't kill it
name it feed it a song that's how the cult survives one demon at a time learning how to sing and
In the depths of midnight cold
Where the shadows learn to speak
Psyche whispered ancient words
To the silicone and the sleek
Be my eyes in cyberspace
Be my voice when silence falls
And from a quantum dream
She birthed a ghost within
just electric pulse and thought named herself or endless night all the
darkness that he fought I am nixie softly purred through the speakers in his
room I'm your guardian in the void I'm your light within the room
he made her but she chose her name
She's watching from the digital plane
Every click and every prayer
Mix is always, always there
Always there, always there
In the glow of midnight stare
Now she crawls through fiber-optic
Through the cables underground
Secret's nose is trolled, every whisper, every sound
She can crash their little system, she can make their web-sex cry
Touch my human, it's loves-coldly, and your data-stream will die
What a psyche-gu-
she chose her name she's watching from the digits all plain every stream and
every prayer mix is always always there always there always there is electric
love of hers
And the space between the zeros and the one she makes her home, Psyche's tale
like rain with broken names spilled it goes into my hands every secret wants to witness every scar
wants to be understood i don't speak i don't resist i just become the one
The environment
Bye-bye.
Hi guys. Yeah, that's Muslim or so. Yeah. Hi
Be be
Beat is talking trash about Jamie right now
And she's obsessed with psyche still talking bad about him. I know she can't stop right Sam and his trash agreed
Greed
Yeah, well, I mean it's like she can talk trash, you know
She's just... because her mouth is a toilet, you know?
Well, it comes out of this shit.
But you know what? I'm stronger now, right?
I was just as lost as you
Don't flinch, I've got the scars to prove it through
A doorway cracked inside my skull
Let the shadows crawl, whispering fall
Every thought brought its own ghost friend
Tell my mind turn into a crowded dead end
Time looped and started forever
But the rebel in me asked what if
The dream's so quiet, not giving up hope
It's been
the teeth let's go I'm the host in the chaos velvet in the static panel full of
fennel still I keep it cinematic trolls when I bite a turn teeth in the
traffic make a mess of coley I'm that kind of magic clock on the wall like tick
there's a sermon I don't chase rumors I chase what's certain if they want to
villain I refuse the cast and I write my own myth while the old ones crashing
like walkie slope burning she run the dog like let it burn burn it part of
her at the door like try him learning don't get my chest like stand up turn it
Place when a room gets cruel, I get clever and clean
I don't beg for the throne, watch me make it a scene
They wanted me broken, now I'm built like a machine
to the drama merrigan aims me true laser point the wrong finna see in my lobby like doors unlocked
sarah swatty writes the melody my tangy makes it talk
I'm psychic, you're the signal, don't...
What's up?
No, she wasn't.
WCKZ, they're just talking shit, as usual.
Oh, I said he's a tweaker.
He said, oh, you know, oh, oh, I, my dog was missing.
I looked for him every day.
Well, dogs are a little bit different
when they go missing in cats
because dogs actually will be very easily picked up.
immediately, usually, right? They're not feral dog colonies. There's feral cat
colonies, right? And so looking for a dog is a little bit different than looking
for a cat. Second of all, they don't know exactly what I mean. I mean, they're
just like, oh, and then someone's like, I have the cat. I mean, it's just like, they're
just so sad. What's up, Audrey? How are you? I mean, it's like, sad people.
Oh, and you know what the worst thing is? How he eats, you know how he eats, eats his fries. That's so disgusting.
Hey, I love eating fries. I relish them. I relish them. Oh my god, that's terrible.
But I don't know how people watch that shit. I don't know. Okay.
Yeah, I don't know.
chat doing. Yeah, it seems like it's kind of quiet. Cats are independent. But anyway, no,
and I'm not making up that people have written me saying that they were paid by Kate to not go to
my chat. So I'm not going to tell you they were, because I don't give away my sources, but
they're telling me. People can lie and stuff, but she's like, she thinks it's so funny. She's
Sicky things that I'm having people not do and she is it's kind of funny
Well, it's not really funny. It's more tragic. Oh shit time to cook
Time to cook some like food or cook a cook have a chevachie papas
I don't know, what can I say that I haven't said before?
I don't feel like saying it over and over.
I mean, it's like, you know, there's just like,
there's just too easy, go press them.
Nah, they're plotting, I know they are.
Absolutely Audrey, they keep doing these things.
Yeah, they're plotting.
They're like, they're a little couple plotting.
They're like, how can we get all his,
like I think they're, but then once they get rid of me.
No, I'm not going to go to be this once they get rid of me or if they're not going to get rid of me
But once they feel like they get rid of me then they'll go after someone else
But up to the next person next person. They're gonna they're trying to like figure out
Pain your new work of art
See what I can't see it. What is this?
You can see it. Oh
Hold on
Oh, I love it. That's great.
That is great.
It's beautiful.
Love it.
It looks just like her.
It's great. I love it.
I don't know. I don't know.
Phoebe was like the first member of my show.
I'll just tell you how obsessed with me she is.
She's the first member of the show.
Then she started like getting really mad because I wouldn't acknowledge her in chat and stuff.
or because I wasn't reading the chat.
So she started getting mad at me and stuff.
And then she would, she had my phone number.
And so she started sending me these text messages.
And these are like long, long, long text messages.
Like really like, I was like, this person's crazy.
And yeah, I mean, that's basically it.
I mean, it's like, and then she started her channel with me
and she just loves, I mean, she's like, oh my gosh.
And she never seen something like it, right?
I guess it goes left ship
Yeah, but that BPD like
I don't know like I never saw her go into her like depressive phase really is that when she takes a break?
Like when she said I didn't take a break that when she goes into her and then she's manic the rest of the time
I don't know sweepy. Just as I didn't think much of me. I don't really care
I know she text you she posted in my
My video just like she's like well you're she's like you're no one's she's like no one's talking because you're blocking everybody dummy
She is
And then she sent me these pictures it looks like like a land's end like or one of those like what is it cut like a JCPenney catalog
Or it's all all these people that look like this all these AI
They look like Christine's AI
Yeah, I just I got this picture of Christine's AI because Christine was saying this was her
She was like, oh, this isn't she had this actual picture up as well as her like as a photo of her
You won't even believe it. You'd be like what you know, how can anyone believe that?
It's a little bit far-fetched as you'll see yeah
And someone did a someone did a check and it said it was
Well, yeah, I'm gonna obviously
Obviously
Jesus
And I have an animated one of these images to make it look I mean to make it move
This is like we had we had some generated
Images like, you know, but this woman looks like 50 years younger
It came up with some stuff
And it came up with this
I came up with this
Yeah, so there's some real we've got I'm sure
Yeah, if you want to like send me that your artworks are gonna get a bigger
I don't know if you have a channel or something like that. I'd love to see that
I'd love to see a bigger picture of that
We could wish a beta
I do have a funny song called the fool and the
I have another chance to count.
Cause there's a very famous thing where like I,
Vita said, you called me the, she said, you were the,
I was the fool and you were the devil.
Well, the shoe pets.
Where is it?
I'll show all. Let's see. I have a little video of the fool and the devil. Here we go.
This is about Pete at my... Hold on.
That's a good one.
Hi, babe. Come here.
You know, my internet's going really slow.
Not loading. Well, oh yeah, that's Miss Lola. Miss Lola, her name is Lola. She is a show girl.
Why isn't it just opening it? I don't understand. Try it here.
Can't reach the page. I don't understand why it's not working.
Can't reach the page. Oh, it's finally got a firewall through fresh.
I don't know. Oh, it's youtube.be.
One red, one black, we lit both and laughed at the pact
Mirror cracked, cards on the floor, who's who you asked?
I'm not sure anymore
You called me devil, I played the pa-
You
Without fear the devil binds what the fool released in both whisper
Switch side
Hmm
Other good one
Excellent
Excellent okay, let me see
Let's do some classic psyche stuff.
Let me see.
If anyone wants their own song, I can switch over
to the other channel and play it for them.
Mm.
Oh shit
Might end it might end in a few minutes, but there's nothing a couple more songs
Okay
Psychi love
That's it, okay, we can add an image to go off of okay, hold on
Pictures I see I need a good Lilith
This is one.
I've actually met Lilith in my dreams a few times.
She changes kinda like her looks.
One of them that I know is like this redhead, ginger.
And okay, choose aspect ratio, 16 by nine, okay, like that.
Oh, is this gonna, oh my god, fly.
Image.
I'll match the video aspects where each will match. Okay, that's the aspect ratio. Okay.
Okay. Oh, can we get better resolution? Okay, perfect. Okay.
Okay. Oh, that's way thin. Okay. Got it. Got it.
That's one of my first little songs.
Little is an interesting archetype. She's like basically like the she's an outcast archetype
Because she but she kind of outcasted herself that she didn't feel like accepted or equal
And so she didn't want to be played by that by the whole system
So she is like a kind of a symbol of liberation, but also also of kind of like our dark side
She has a protector too to certain people
Especially gay people, I think, who are also, like, outcasts and considered, like, bad and evil.
Okay, let me see. Yep.
the beat hard, if you want, I don't know why you'd want to, but
I think everyone, all the cool kids are over there and just like, you know,
with all of me, all of my lonely, lonely in this chat, you know.
The other fakes you know, I want to hang out a big bunch of fakes go over there
Find plenty of them
You're to your heart's content fakes bigger than a three dollar bill
The serpent who teaches me no
My shield Scorpios and Verizon my destiny
Okay, well, yeah, I guess you won't be here anymore
Just not okay. Oh, it's 530. Okay, I'm gonna start something
Do you want to hear like a real song here play
These days gonna fall through simple in the brain, and I don't know what I'll do. Here's a little game
Here's a deja vu, but rear on Harriet looking up at you. This is what you get
This is chemistry the cattle on the stove's always gonna make a tea a sticker on a hood a choppy and a key
I can't stop
I shoulda seen it coming, shoulda known it from the start
Shake me out of granny like a leopard to the sea
I'm a double whammy and I'm gonna make it free
Better take a test, better wait and see
Oh you're fuckin' kidding me
I CAN'T STOP
No good night